Finding Aid for the Nellie Burns Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Nellie Burns Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0064
.63 linear feet
Biography
Nellie Burns was the daughter of a Jasper County, Tennessee physician. She may have attended Peabody College and was employed for some period at the Jasper County post office.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of Nellie Burns diaries which contain business transactions, social interactions, and her daily activities.
- Diary:, August 28, 1900-October 22, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Diary:, May 7, 1924-May 19, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Diary:, October 14, 1924-October 23, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Diary:, April 2, 1925-April 13, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Diary:, February 1, 1926-February 14, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Diary:, April 18, 1926-April 28, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Diary:, December 3, 1926-December 6, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Diary:, June 1, 1926-June 28, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Diary:, March 1, 1927-March 19, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Diary:, March 22, 1927-April 11, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Diary:, April 12, 1927-April 30, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Diary:, June 22, 1927-July 2, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Diary:, March 8, 1928-March 29, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Diary:, April 4, 1928-April 14, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Diary:, April 11-April 16, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Diary:, April 26-May 6, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Diary:, July 5-July 22, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)